Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Requisition Files /4211
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Requisition Files
1993-1994
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
Martin P. Catherwood Library
Harper, Shirley
Law, Gordon T., Jr.
/4211
8 cubic feet
8 linear ft.
Records (documents).
8051468
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, August 13, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 04, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4139: Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files /4169: Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files /4172: Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files /4178: Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files /4192: Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files /4201: Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files /4272: Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files /4272 P: Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Photographs
Law, Gordon T., Jr.; Harper, Shirley F.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Library
8051468
- A general thru Carswell Legal Pub, 1993-1994.. (Box 1)
  - REQUISITIONS "A" GENERAL (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Academy of Political Science (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - ADMINISTRATIVE MANAGEMENT SOCIETY Requisitions (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - ADVANCED IMAGE MANAGEMENT Requisitions (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - AFL-CIO Requisitions (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - AFRICAN IMPRINT LIBRARY SERVICES (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Airborne Express (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - AKATEEMINEN KIRKJAKAUPPA Requisitions (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - ALMQVIST & WISKELL INTERNATIONAL Requisitions (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - AMERICAN (GENERAL) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - AMERICAN ARBITRATION ASSOCIATION Requisitions (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - ARL OFFICE MANAGEMENT STUDIES Requisitions (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - ASSOCIATION OF NEGOTIATORS AND CONTRACT ADMINISTRATORS Requisitions (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - ARL: Association of Research Library (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Aspen Publishers, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - AUDIO-VIDEO DISTRIBUTORS (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - AUDIO VISUAL SYSTEMS, INC. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - AUSTRALIA (general) Requisitions (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - AUX AMATEURS DE LIVRES INTERNATIONAL Requisitions (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - A/V Distributors (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "B" - GENERAL Requisitions (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Bach, Susan LTDA (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - BALLEN Requisitions (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Basefsky, Stuart (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - BENDER, MATTHEW Requisitions (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - BENNETT, JAMES Requisitions (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - BERNAN Requisitions (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - BIBLIOGRAPHIC RETRIEVAL SERVICES Requisitions (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - BLACKWELL Requisitions (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - BOLERIUM (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Books From Mexico (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - BOTES LIBRARY Requisitions (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - R. R. BOWKER Requisitions (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - BRODART Requisitions (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - BURAFF PUBLICATIONS (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - THE BUREAU OF NATIONAL AFFAIRS Requisitions (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - BNA BOOKS Requisitions (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Business and Legal Reports (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Arnold Busck Export Division (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - BUTTERWORTHS Requisitions (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - "C" - GENERAL Requisitions (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - California, State of (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - CALIFORNIA, UNIVERSITY OF Requisitions (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - CALLAGHAN & COMPANY Requisitions (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Cambiero, Fernando Garcia (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - CANADA - GENERAL Requisitions (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - CANADA LAW BOOK INC. Requisitions (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - CANADIAN GOVERNMENT PUBLISHING CENTRE Requisitions (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - CARIBBEAN IMPRINT LIBRARY SERVICES (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - CARSWELL LEGAL PUBLICATIONS (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Casalini, Libri thru Executive Telcom, 1993-1994. (Box 2)
  - CASALINI LIBRI Requisitions (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Center on Budget & Policy Priorities (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - CENTRAL NEW YORK COPIERS Requisitions (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - CHALLENGE INDUSTRIES Requisitions (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - CLARK, BOARDMAN, CALLAHAN Requisitions (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Colorado Dept. of Labor Employment (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Columbia, University of (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - COMMERCE CLEARING HOUSE Requisitions (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - COMPUSEVE INC. Requisitions (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - COMPUTING CENTER Requisitions (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - CONFERENCE BOARD Requisitions (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - CONGRESSIONAL INFORMATION SERVICE Requisitions (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - CONGRESSIONAL QUARTERLY, INC. Requisitions (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - CONSERVATION INFORMATION NETWORK (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - COPY MACHINE SUPPLY (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Copyright Clearance Center (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - CORNELL DAILY SUN Requisitions (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - CORNELL INFORMATION TECHNOLOGIES Requisitions (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - CORNELL UNIVERSITY Requisitions (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - CORNELL UNIVERSITY - INSURANCE Requisitions (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - CORNELL UNIVERSITY LIBRARIES ADMINISTRATIVE OPERATIONS Requisitions (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - CORNELL UNIVERSITY LIBRARIES DIALOG INFORMATION SERVICES, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - C.U.L. DIS Knight-Ridder, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - C.U.L. DIS Knight-Ridder, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - CORNELL UNIVERSITY LIBRARIES MESSENGER EXPENSE Requisitions (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - CORNELL UNIVERSITY LIBRARIES RLG-RLIN, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - CORNELL UNIVERSITY LIBRARIES RLG-RLIN, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - CORNELL UNIVERSITY LIBRARIES RLG-RLIN, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - CORNELL UNIVERSITY MAINTENANCE & SERVICE OPERATIONS Requisitions (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - CORNELL UNIVERSITY STATE COLLEGE FLEET Requisitions (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Cornell University Stores Enterprises, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - CU STORES ENTERPRISES, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Cornell University Stores Enterprises, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - COUTTS LIBRARY SERVICE Requisitions (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - CROWN PUBLICATIONS (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - CUP Services (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - "D" - GENERAL Requisitions (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Dankert, Philip (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - DATA "General" Requisitions (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - DEMCO Requisitions (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - DOCUMENTS INDEX-GUIDE TO U.S. GOVT. SERIALS & PERIODICALS Requisitions (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - DOW JONES INFORMATION SERVICE Requisitions (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - "E" - GENERAL Requisitions (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - EBSCO SUBSCRIPTION SERVICES Requisitions, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - EBSCO SUBSCRIPTION SERVICE Requisitions, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - EBSCO SUBSCRIPTION SERVICES Requisitions, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - EBSCO SUBSCRIPTION SERVICE Online (EBSCONET) Service, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Employment Policies Institute (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - 83 BROWN ROAD SILEY REAL ESTATE SERVICES, INC. Requisitions (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - EXECUTIVE TELECOM Requisitions (Box 2, Folder 50)
- F General thru Interdepartmental Orders (Debits) 93. (Box 3)
  - "F" - GENERAL Requisitions (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - FEDERAL EXPRESS Requisitions (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - ANN FILARDO Requisitions (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Finlay, Constance (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - "G" - GENERAL Requisitions (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - GALE RESEARCH COMPANY (acct. 126233) Requisitions (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - GAYLORD BROTHERS Requisitions (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Gerold & Company (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - GREENWOOD PRESS Requisitions (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - GNOMAN Requisitions (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - "H" - GENERAL Requisitions (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - HAMILTON, ALEXANDER CORP. Requisitions (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - HARRASSOWITZ, OTTO Requisitions, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - HARRASSOWITZ, OTTO Requisitions, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - HARRISON COMPANY Requisitions (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - HAWAII, UNIVERSITY OF (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - HERITAGE PUBLISHING HOUSE Requisitions (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - HEWITT ASSOCIATES Requisitions (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - HIGHSMITH Requisitions (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - HOLLINGER CORPORATION Requisitions (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Human Resource Systems Professionals (HRSP Adm. Office) (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - "I" - GENERAL Requisitions (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - INCOMES DATA SERVICES LTD. ENGLAND Requisitions (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - INDUSTRIAL RELATIONS RESEARCH ASSOC. Requisitions (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - INFORMATION ON DEMAND Requisitions (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - INPUT CULTURE COMPANY, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - INPUT CULTURE COMPANY, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - INPUT CULTURE COMPANY, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - INSIGHTS Requisitions (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - INTERDEPARTMENTAL ORDERS - CREDITS, 1990-1994 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - INTERDEPARTMENTAL ORDERS - DEBITS, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - INTERDEPARTMENTAL ORDERS - DEBITS, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Interdepartmental Orders, Debits thru Mead Data Corp., 1993-1994. (Box 4)
  - INTERDEPARTMENTAL ORDERS - DEBITS, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - INTERNATIONAL FOUNDATION OF EMPLOYEE BENEFIT PLANS - Membership Requisitions (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - INTERNATIONAL INDUSTRIAL RELATIONS ASSOCIATION Requisitions (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - INTERNATIONAL LABOUR OFFICE Requisitions (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - INTERNATIONAL PERSONNEL MANAGEMENT ASSOCIATION Requisitions (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - International Social Security Assoc. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - "J" - GENERAL Requisitions (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - JAI PRESS INC. Requisitions (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - JAPAN PUBLICATIONS TRADING CO., LTD. Requisitions (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - JOURNAL ENTRIES Requisitions, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - JOURNAL ENTRIES Requisitions, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - JOURNAL ENTRIES Requisitions, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - "K" - GENERAL Requisitions (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Labor Market Information Services (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - LABOR RELATIONS PRESS (LRP) Requisitions (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - "L" - GENERAL Requisitions (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - LABOR RESEARCH ASSOCIATION Requisitions (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Law, Gordon T. (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Law Journal Press (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - THE LAWYERS CO-OP PUBLISHING COMPANY Requisitions (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - LENZ & RIECKER Requisitions (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Lexis - Nexis (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - LIBRARY OF CONGRESS Requisitions (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Libreria Passim, S. A. (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Linardi, A. & Risso, J. (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Little, Brown and Co. (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Livraria Portugal (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - "M" - GENERAL Requisitions (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - MAINE DEPT. OF LABOR Requisitions (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Manos, Paulette (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - MEAD DATA CORPORATION Requisitions (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Michigan Library Consortium thru Soldier Creek Press, 1994. (Box 5)
  - MICHIGAN LIBRARY CONSORTIUM Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - MICHIGAN, UNIVERSITY OF Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Micro Warehouse, Inc. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 3M COMPANY (Minn. Mining & Manu.) Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - MISCO Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - MIT SLOAN SCHOOL Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Morley, Barbara (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - "N" - GENERAL, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - "N" - GENERAL, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - "N" - GENERAL, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - NACO ELECTRONICS Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - NATIONAL AUDIO-VISUAL SUPPLY Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - NATIONAL BUREAU OF ECONOMIC RESEARCH Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - NATIONAL CENTER FOR EMPLOYEE OWNERSHIP Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - NATIONAL COMMITTEE ON PAY EQUITY Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - National Conference of State Legislature (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - NATIONAL REGISTER PUBLISHING COMPANY Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - NATIONAL SAFE WORKPLACE INSTITUTE Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - National Safety Council (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - National Technical Information Service (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - THE NATIONAL UNDERWRITER COMPANY (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Neely, Gail (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - NEW ENGLAND LEGAL PUBLISHERS Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - NewsNet (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - NewsNet (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - NEWSPAPER DELIVERY SERVICE - ITHACA (New York Times) Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - NEW YORK - GENERAL Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - NEW ZEALAND - GENERAL Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - NIJHOFF INTERNATIONAL Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Nisly, Hope (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - "O" - GENERAL Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - OCED Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - OPINIONS PRESS Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Oxford University Press (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - "P" - GENERAL Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Panmun Book Co., Ltd. (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - PC CONNECTION Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - THE PAIGE COMPANY Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - PANEL PUBLISHERS, INC. Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - PASSIM Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - PBS VIDEO Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - PERSONAL BIBLIOGRAPHIC SOFTWARE Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - PERSONNEL MANAGEMENT ABSTRACTS Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Pfeiffer & Co. (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - PRENTICE HALL Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - PUBLIC AFFAIRS INFORMATION SERVICE, INC. Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - PUBLIC INTEREST PUBLICATIONS Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Puvill Libros (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - "Q" - GENERAL Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - "R" - GENERAL Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - REED REFERENCE PUBLISHING Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Reeves, Sharon (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - ROCKEFELLER INSTITUTE Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Rockhurst College Continuing Ed CTR (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - "S" - GENERAL Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - SAGE PUBLICATIONS INC. Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - SENTRY BUSINESS PRODUCTS Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - SHEPARD'S CITATIONS Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Society for HRM (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Soldier Creek Press (Box 5, Folder 60)
- South Carolina Employment Security Commission thru Yankee Book Peddler, 1993-1994. (Box 6)
  - SOUTH CAROLINA EMPLOYMENT SECURITY COMMISSION Requisitions (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - SOUTH CENTRAL RESEARCH LIBRARY COUNCIL Requisitions (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - SPECIAL LIBRARIES ASSOCIATION Requisitions (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - STATE HISTORICAL SOCIETY OF WISCONSIN (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - STATISTICS CANADA Requisitions (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Strassberg, Richard (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Sweden, general (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - "T" - GENERAL Requisitions (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - TNT RED STAR EXPRESS INC. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Thomson Professional Publishing Can (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Thorold, Frank (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - TOMPKINS-SENECA-TIOGA B.O.C.E.S. Requisitions (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - TOTAL INFORMATION Requisitions (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - TRIANGLE BOOK SHOP Requisitions (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - "U" - GENERAL Requisitions (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - UNIPUB Requisitions (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - UNITED NATIONS Requisitions (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - UNITED STATES - GENERAL Requisitions (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - U.S. GOVERNMENT PRINTING OFFICE ACCT#0732636 Requisitions (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - UNIVERSITY - GENERAL Requisitions (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - UNIVERSITY MICROFILMS Requisitions (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - "V" - GENERAL Requisitions (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - VANCE Requisitions (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - VU/TEXT Requisitions (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - "W" - GENERAL Requisitions (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - WEST PUBLISHING Requisitions (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - WARREN, GORHAM & LAMONT Requisitions (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Washington, general (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - WASHINGTON RESEARCHERS LTD Requisitions (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - WILEY, JOHN & SONS Requisitions (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - WILSON, H.W. COMPANY Requisitions (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - WORD PERFECT CORP. (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - World Bank Publications (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Yankee Book Peddler, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Yankee Book Peddler, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - YANKEE BOOK PEDDLER Requisitions, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - "XYZ" (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Xerox (Box 6, Folder 38)
- A-Information, 1994-1995.. (Box 7)
  - American Statistical Association - Advanced Image Management (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - AFL-CIO Dept. of Professional Employ - Alliance to End Childhood Poisoning (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Asian & Pacific Developmental Centre - Matthew Bender & Company, Inc. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - James Bennett PTY LTD - Bureau of National Affairs, Inc. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Arnold Busck Export Division - Colorado Dept. of Labor & Employment (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Continuing Education of the Bar - Casalini Libri (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Center on Budget & Policy Priorities - Conference Board, Inc. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Congressional Information Service - Cornell Information Technologies (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Cornell University Library folder 1 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Cornell University Library folder 2 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Cornell University Library folder 3 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - C.U. Stores Enterprises folder 1 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - C.U. Stores Enterprises folder 2 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - C.U. Stores Enterprises folder 3 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Crown Publications, Inc. - Employment Policies Institute (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - EBSCO Subscription Services, Inc. (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Fisher Books - Gateway 2000 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Gale Research Inc. - HIAA Distribution Center (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Hawaii Labor Relations Board - Joseph D. Henry (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Heritage Publishing House - Information/Reference Group (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Input-Z, 1994-1995.. (Box 8)
  - Input Culture Company (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Interdepartmental Order (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - International Labour Office - Japan Publications Trading Co., LTD (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Journal Voucher (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Kagi Shareware - Little, Brown & Company (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - LRP Publications - Law Journal Press (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Lexis-Nexis (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Linaroi - Micro Logic Corporation (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - OIRSA Distribuidora Internacional - Nico Mak Computing Inc. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - National Network for Women's Employment - NCSCBHEP (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - New Zealand Export Books - Progressive Policy Institute (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Pritchett & Associates, Inc. - Public Interest Publications (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Puvill Libros - Remington Products Co. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Reed Reference Publishing Company - Starnine Technologies Inc. (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - State Historical Society of Wisconsin - Thomson Professional Publishing Can (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - TPS Electronics Inc. - United Parcel Service (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - U.S. Dept. of Labor - University Publications of America (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Voyager - World Bank Publications (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Research Association of Washington - York University (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Yankee Book Peddler (Box 8, Folder 20)